[
    {
        "question": "4 × 3 = ?",
        "choice1": "10",
        "choice2": "11",
        "choice3": "12",
        "choice4": "13",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 6 = ?",
        "choice1": "25",
        "choice2": "30",
        "choice3": "35",
        "choice4": "40",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 2 = ?",
        "choice1": "12",
        "choice2": "14",
        "choice3": "16",
        "choice4": "18",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 4 = ?",
        "choice1": "28",
        "choice2": "30",
        "choice3": "32",
        "choice4": "34",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 5 = ?",
        "choice1": "40",
        "choice2": "45",
        "choice3": "50",
        "choice4": "55",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 6 = ?",
        "choice1": "30",
        "choice2": "32",
        "choice3": "34",
        "choice4": "36",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 9 = ?",
        "choice1": "25",
        "choice2": "26",
        "choice3": "27",
        "choice4": "28",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 2 = ?",
        "choice1": "22",
        "choice2": "23",
        "choice3": "24",
        "choice4": "25",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 3 = ?",
        "choice1": "30",
        "choice2": "31",
        "choice3": "32",
        "choice4": "33",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 10 = ?",
        "choice1": "90",
        "choice2": "95",
        "choice3": "100",
        "choice4": "105",
        "answer": 3
    }
]
